<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>john gitahi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on john gitahi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024, John Gitahi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 10:08:39 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dilemma of Virtue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 10:08:39 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it wickedness? Is it weakness? You decide&#xA;— &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Kendrick Lamar&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a question we must ask ourselves today more than ever: What are our goals and what means will we use to attain them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is common knowledge that the world today is cruel and unfair. Every man is more concerned about his own welfare than for the welfare of others. In contemporary society, it is evident that virtue is not rewarded and promoted whereas vice is rewarded and promoted. For instance, gambling and saving. Saving has been punished with low interest rates and high inflation rates. Gambling has been rewarded with promises of winning high jackpots and chronic media endorsement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Good Doctor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-good-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-good-doctor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a student nurse during clinical rotations, I am beginning to gain a deeper appreciation for the profound nature of healthcare. I am beginning to understand that medicine is a calling that demands devotion. When I become a doctor, I&amp;rsquo;ll need to approach my work with an almost sacred dedication, knowing my decisions will directly affect patients lives in the long-term. This means my medical judgements must be well-informed and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
