<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>john gitahi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on john gitahi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024, John Gitahi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 10:26:50 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal reflections on HIV/AIDS: My journey through Stigma and Understanding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-hiv/aids-my-journey-through-stigma-and-understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 10:26:50 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-hiv/aids-my-journey-through-stigma-and-understanding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HIV was first correctly diagnosed in the early 1980s in America. From that time onwards, human society has done much to prevent HIV infeciton and mitigate the effects of HIV on the human body. Prevention campaigns have promoted faithfullness in marriage, sex abstinence, condom usage, and more. Highly Active Antiretroviral Therapy (HAART) has been designed to alleviate the effects of HIV on the human body and to prevent eventual progression to the state of AIDS. To date, HIV remains one of the most studied microbial agents. Alot of insights have been garnered on medical management, nursing care, and general prevention and control from this extensive research.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilemma of Virtue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 10:08:39 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it wickedness? Is it weakness? You decide&#xA;— &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Kendrick Lamar&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a question we must ask ourselves today more than ever: What are our goals and what means will we use to attain them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is common knowledge that the world today is cruel and unfair. Every man is more concerned about his own welfare than for the welfare of others. In contemporary society, it is evident that virtue is not rewarded and promoted whereas vice is rewarded and promoted. For instance, gambling and saving. Saving has been punished with low interest rates and high inflation rates. Gambling has been rewarded with promises of winning high jackpots and chronic media endorsement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
