<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>john gitahi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on john gitahi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024, John Gitahi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 12:31:26 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A year in AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/a-year-in-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 12:31:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/a-year-in-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To myself,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know you have tried to wrap your head around how AI systems work many times. This is your third time. The last time you promised to either master it or abandon it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well today&amp;rsquo;s a new day. And I think now more than ever you need to understand how this stuff works. Because I trust you have a role in the development of these novo intelligent systems. You learned how to program computers and now I want you to learn how to design and make AI in a year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I wont try psilocybin or any drugs now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/why-i-wont-try-psilocybin-or-any-drugs-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 12:24:50 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/why-i-wont-try-psilocybin-or-any-drugs-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eric Fromm in his book The Art Of Loving shares that as humans, we are constantly seeking to quench the thirst of separateness and loneliness; that separateness is what breeds anxiety. Many people try to satisfy this need by using drugs and sex. I understand what he meant by that because I am currently going through that phase when I feel so overwhelmed and separated and the next thing that I can think of is either to find a partner or use drugs to cope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Order</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/beautiful-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:40:46 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/beautiful-order/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Consider this, nature is intricately complicated yet so simple and orderly. It is the perfect representation of &amp;ldquo;Simplicity on the other side of complexity&amp;rdquo;. This order we observe - explained by rules such as those of genetics - map disorder to order&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my own life, I strive to embrace disorder,to  enter the forest of disorder and evolve through it. I believe that in the grand scheme of things, I will emerge as a beautiful representation of order, just like nature itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal reflections on my goals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-my-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:43:50 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-my-goals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am reminding myself that the best way to live is to stay focused on my goals. I have been rudderless for the past two years — not because I had no set goals or did not work on my goals, but because I was careless with how I executed plans. Especially the short-term goals. It is a sad realization which has been difficult to confront.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make it more relatable, I have been lacking in discipline. It comes to the basics:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal reflections on HIV/AIDS: My journey through Stigma and Understanding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-hiv/aids-my-journey-through-stigma-and-understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 10:26:50 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-reflections-on-hiv/aids-my-journey-through-stigma-and-understanding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HIV was first correctly diagnosed in the early 1980s in America. From that time onwards, human society has done much to prevent HIV infeciton and mitigate the effects of HIV on the human body. Prevention campaigns have promoted faithfullness in marriage, sex abstinence, condom usage, and more. Highly Active Antiretroviral Therapy (HAART) has been designed to alleviate the effects of HIV on the human body and to prevent eventual progression to the state of AIDS. To date, HIV remains one of the most studied microbial agents. Alot of insights have been garnered on medical management, nursing care, and general prevention and control from this extensive research.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilemma of Virtue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 10:08:39 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dilemma-of-virtue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it wickedness? Is it weakness? You decide&#xA;— &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Kendrick Lamar&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a question we must ask ourselves today more than ever: What are our goals and what means will we use to attain them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is common knowledge that the world today is cruel and unfair. Every man is more concerned about his own welfare than for the welfare of others. In contemporary society, it is evident that virtue is not rewarded and promoted whereas vice is rewarded and promoted. For instance, gambling and saving. Saving has been punished with low interest rates and high inflation rates. Gambling has been rewarded with promises of winning high jackpots and chronic media endorsement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
